# Logan Parker

Loganparker.ca Vancouver, British Columbia

Logan@loganparker.ca

## **Profile**

Enthusiastic and adaptable BCom graduate from the University of British Columbia with a specialization in Finance and Real Estate. Driven by a desire for overcoming obstacles and achieving goals in both personal and professional settings. Thrives in collaborative and independent environments.

## Education

**Bachelor of Commerce,** Finance and Real Estate (Honours) University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC

Completed April 2016

• Dean's Honour Roll 2015, 2016.

# **Work Experience**

Associate, SchoolSoft Inc., Calgary, AB (Contract) September 2012—August 2013, August 2016—Present

- Testing the new online student-permission-form software on an ongoing basis, reporting major issues and changes directly to the founders.
- Creating and distributing invoices on an ongoing basis to clients in North America and Europe.
- Configured 250 customers' accounts for the parent-teacher-interview scheduling software.

Investment Analyst, Premise Properties, Vancouver, BC

May 2015—August 2015

- Created and maintained a model in Excel to value a project in the Lower Mainland. Work completed was used to attract an equity partner, secure financing, and reach a decision to buy.
- Led the due diligence process on the sale of a major commercial property in Vancouver.
- Analyzed all current real estate investments within the company in order to assess current asset value and performance versus expected value and performance.

**Operations Manager,** Cowichan Lake Marina, Lake Cowichan, BC (Seasonal) May 2010—August 2014

- Ordered, managed, and sold \$25,000 worth of merchandise per season for the marina's retail store.
- Met sales and cost-cutting goals through constant communication with suppliers, staff, and owners.

# **Activities and Community Involvement**

Vice President & External Public Relations, UBC Ski and Snowboard Club April 2013—March 2015

- Raised \$2,500 for Vancouver Adaptive Snow Sports (VASS) by organizing and executing a skiing and snowboarding contest at UBC with over 400 spectators and 40 contestants.
- Built and maintained a relationship with 28 sponsors throughout the calendar year for the UBC Ski and Snowboard Club—one of UBC's largest student-run clubs.

## **Skills and Interests**

Skills: Presenting and public speaking, Microsoft Office, basic HTML and CSS, basic Python, basic SQL.

Interests: Cycling: After graduating from UBC I cycled 3,100 kilometers from Vancouver, BC

to the border of Mexico near San Diego.

Surfing: I spent kindergarten to grade five growing up near Santa Cruz, California,

where I learned to surf and continue to do so on Vancouver Island.

Traveling: I spent the summer following graduation traveling USA and Europe.